<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Abhishek kumar Azad</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Abhishek kumar Azad</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Choose the Right Power Supply for Your PC</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When you’re preparing to build a new PC, the first topics on your mind are likely powerful multi-core processors, fancy high-end graphics cards, ultra-fast NVMe storage, or maybe even unique case lighting and effects. But one component that often fails to get the attention it deserves is the power supply. After all, virtually every other component in your PC can be affected by the type, quality, and capabilities of your PSU.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That makes the process of choosing the right power supply just as important as any other component. Therefore, here’s a quick high-level overview of the factors you should consider when looking at power supplies for your next PC build.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOOM The Dark Ages Tested: 13 GPUs Benchmarked To Hell And Back</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DOOM is back—and it&amp;rsquo;s never looked meaner. &lt;strong&gt;DOOM The Dark Ages&lt;/strong&gt; is the latest installment in Id Software&amp;rsquo;s iconic franchise, bringing a brutal blend of medieval mayhem and modern firepower. Powered by the &lt;strong&gt;id Tech 8 engine&lt;/strong&gt;, this entry trades Mars for dark fantasy while keeping the brutal combat, metal soundtrack, and silky-smooth performance that DOOM is known for.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Naturally, we had to see how it runs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could couples therapy be right for you?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/more-rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/more-rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Marriage can be one of life&amp;rsquo;s greatest joys, but it&amp;rsquo;s no secret that staying together takes work. For couples looking to strengthen their bond or navigate challenges, therapy can offer a path toward deeper connection and understanding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-couples-therapy&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  What is couples therapy?&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#what-is-couples-therapy&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Couples therapy is a form of counseling that involves both partners in a relationship. This form of therapy is provided by a licensed therapist who is trained to help couples resolve conflicts they are experiencing. Couples therapy for married couples may be called marital therapy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 ways to build brain-boosting social connections</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mind &amp;amp; Mood&lt;br&gt;&#xA;3 ways to build brain-boosting social connections&lt;br&gt;&#xA;September 27, 2024&lt;br&gt;&#xA;By Kelly Bilodeau, Former Executive Editor, Harvard Women&amp;rsquo;s Health Watch&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Reviewed by Howard E. LeWine, MD, Chief Medical Editor, Harvard Health Publishing; Editorial Advisory Board Member, Harvard Health Publishing&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Two smiling women on a walk together outdoors, they&amp;rsquo;re holding umbrellas&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re careful about your diet. You exercise diligently and try to get enough sleep each night. But you may have forgotten to add one ingredient for a healthy body and brain to your list: a good social life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staying Healthy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Living your best life&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Two Harvard doctors in their 70s and 80s share their wisdom about how to make the most of your remaining years.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;August 1, 2024&lt;br&gt;&#xA;By Matthew Solan, Executive Editor, Harvard Men&amp;rsquo;s Health Watch&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Reviewed by Howard E. LeWine, MD, Chief Medical Editor, Harvard Health Publishing; Editorial Advisory Board Member, Harvard Health Publishing&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;photo of a senior man on a hike standing with his arms outstretched, celebrating the experience and being in the outdoors&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Your Own Resilience Plan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/resilience-strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/resilience-strategies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Build Your Own Resilience Plan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;Three strategies to help you move forward when you&amp;rsquo;re stressed, burned out, anxious, or sad&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Reviewed by Howard E. LeWine, MD, Chief Medical Editor, Harvard Health Publishing; Editorial Advisory Board Member, Harvard Health Publishing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nantucket — a 14-mile-long island off Massachusetts — has a 40-point resiliency plan to withstand the effects of climate change. Similarly, individuals can benefit from building personal resilience plans to deal with life&amp;rsquo;s challenges, big and small. But what exactly is resilience, and how can we cultivate it?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can AI Answer Medical Questions Better Than Your Doctor?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/html-and-css-only-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/html-and-css-only-tabs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last year, headlines describing a study about artificial intelligence (AI) were eye-catching, to say the least:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;ChatGPT Rated as Better Than Real Doctors for Empathy, Advice&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;The AI will see you now: ChatGPT provides higher quality answers and is more empathetic than a real doctor, study finds&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;Is AI Better Than A Doctor? ChatGPT Outperforms Physicians In Compassion And Quality Of Advice&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At first glance, the idea that a chatbot using AI might be able to generate good answers to patient questions isn&amp;rsquo;t surprising. After all, ChatGPT boasts that it passed a final exam for a Wharton MBA, wrote a book in a few hours, and composed original music.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But showing more empathy than your doctor? Ouch. Before assigning final honors on quality and empathy to either side, let&amp;rsquo;s take a second look.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One way to combat loneliness? Strengthen relationships you already have</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One way to combat loneliness? Strengthen relationships you already have&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;January 3, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;By &lt;em&gt;Lisa Catanese, ELS, Health Writer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Reviewed by &lt;em&gt;Robert H. Shmerling, MD&lt;/em&gt;, Senior Faculty Editor, Harvard Health Publishing; Editorial Advisory Board Member, Harvard Health Publishing&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A loneliness epidemic in the U.S. is taking a toll on people&amp;rsquo;s physical and mental health. Mental health problems linked to loneliness include higher rates of anxiety, depression, suicide, anger, and violence. Loneliness also impacts physical health, contributing to an increased risk of heart disease, stroke, high blood pressure, infection, diabetes, dementia, and early death.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The healing power of kindness </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mermaid-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mermaid-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Staying Healthy&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The healing power of kindness&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Being kind isn&amp;rsquo;t just gratifying — it&amp;rsquo;s a path to greater well-being.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;April 1, 2025&lt;br&gt;&#xA;By Maureen Salamon, Executive Editor, Harvard Women&amp;rsquo;s Health Watch&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Reviewed by Toni Golen, MD, Editor in Chief, Harvard Women&amp;rsquo;s Health Watch; Editorial Advisory Board Member, Harvard Health Publishing; Contributor&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A group of people volunteering at a food drive, filling a box with food items.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every year, Tyler VanderWeele chooses a six-week span to do things for others that might ordinarily seem too inconvenient. His good deeds are many and varied: he might give a friend an unexpected gift, invite someone out for coffee, set aside time at work to support a colleague, or bring a family member&amp;rsquo;s favorite food to the dinner table.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
