<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Markdown on Abhishek kumar Azad</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/markdown/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Markdown on Abhishek kumar Azad</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/markdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One way to combat loneliness? Strengthen relationships you already have</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One way to combat loneliness? Strengthen relationships you already have&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;January 3, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;By &lt;em&gt;Lisa Catanese, ELS, Health Writer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Reviewed by &lt;em&gt;Robert H. Shmerling, MD&lt;/em&gt;, Senior Faculty Editor, Harvard Health Publishing; Editorial Advisory Board Member, Harvard Health Publishing&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A loneliness epidemic in the U.S. is taking a toll on people&amp;rsquo;s physical and mental health. Mental health problems linked to loneliness include higher rates of anxiety, depression, suicide, anger, and violence. Loneliness also impacts physical health, contributing to an increased risk of heart disease, stroke, high blood pressure, infection, diabetes, dementia, and early death.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The healing power of kindness </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mermaid-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mermaid-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Staying Healthy&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The healing power of kindness&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Being kind isn&amp;rsquo;t just gratifying — it&amp;rsquo;s a path to greater well-being.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;April 1, 2025&lt;br&gt;&#xA;By Maureen Salamon, Executive Editor, Harvard Women&amp;rsquo;s Health Watch&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Reviewed by Toni Golen, MD, Editor in Chief, Harvard Women&amp;rsquo;s Health Watch; Editorial Advisory Board Member, Harvard Health Publishing; Contributor&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A group of people volunteering at a food drive, filling a box with food items.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every year, Tyler VanderWeele chooses a six-week span to do things for others that might ordinarily seem too inconvenient. His good deeds are many and varied: he might give a friend an unexpected gift, invite someone out for coffee, set aside time at work to support a colleague, or bring a family member&amp;rsquo;s favorite food to the dinner table.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
